## THANG LE

Soi 14, Ratchada, Huya Khwang, Bangkok|Mobile: 0805684902 | Iequocthang45@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Professional web developer with 3+ years experience in designing, developing and implementing websites. Combining with multiple related technologies to build effective and high performance systems. Able to work in various parts in web developing process from frontend to backend.

# **Highlights**

- Life-long learner, keep improving in both technical knowledge and personal perspectives.
- Do the best possible to help the team archive their goals.
- Work well under pressure, optimistic and open-minded

# **Experience**

March 2016 - PRESENT

### Excel Bangkok, Bangkok - C# developer

- Developing Smart Pension System consists of web applications and window services.
- Working as a full-stack developer in a Scrum (Agile) team.
- Interacting directly with product owner from Norway to get requirements.
- Designed a parallelism processing flow to improve performance of the application.
- Working with .NET framework, SQL server, Javascript, etc. to build the system.

September 2015 - January 2016

#### Business online PCL, Bangkok - System Analysis

- Developed websites to manage customers for banking industry
- Analysed database systems, requirements from users to customize the product for Vietnam market.

August 2012 - July 2013

### Aswig Solutions, Hochiminh, Vietnam - Software engineer

- Developed web services for SQL databases.
- Integrated web pages for product management systems
- Worked with .NET framework as the main technology.

September 2011 - July 2012

#### ERM System, Hochiminh, Vietnam - Web Developer

- Developed web application for property management.
- Responsible for frontend and backend of web applications and social plugins

Worked with ASP.NET, MVC, SQL servers..

# **Education**

August 2013 - July 2015

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang, Bangkok - Master of Computing

Dissertation: Brain-computer Interface.

August 2007 - April 2012

HCM National University of Technology, Vietnam - Bachelor of Engineering

Dissertation: Security visualization - Security flaws detection. Honor program

## **Skills**

- Strong programming skills in .NET related technology (C#, ASP.NET, WCF, MVC, Web api, SignalR), Microsoft SQL server, html, Jquery, javascript, bootstrap css.
- Strong analyzing skill in OOP and database systems
- Experienced and learning knowledge in Angular, MongoDB, Javascript, Nodejs (Mean js), Java, C/C++,PHP.
- English degree: IELTS 7.5 (2015)